<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--Do not forget to include this in any locale specific folders for translation-->

    <!--In the following array put your changelog items
    Take as many lines as you need.
    Add as many items as you want or delete some if those are too many
    This order is how they will appear in the dialog
    Make any order you want from top to bottom-->
    <string-array name="changelog_items">
        <item>Ability to use Google Assitant with any of the 2 included home longpress framework</item>
        <item>All individual colors or same color, with option to use tint at the same time.</item>
        <item>Ability to assign Google Assitant to any of the device key - assign from all virtual buttons, screen swipe, screen sweep with any framework selected</item>
        <item>Use Google Assitant without setting country to US</item>
        <item>Quick Toggle colors mod</item>
        <item>Quick Toggle Text mod</item>
        <item>Global switch to restore all notification colors to stock for theme applications and original stock look</item>
        <item>Removed ON/OFF from switches in settings for good application of themes</item>
        <item>Added color option for search text with global restore</item>
        <item>Lockscreen statusbar clock hidden for Potato clock</item>
        <item>Lockscreen statusbar clock hidden for Phronesis clock</item>
        <item>Charger connect animation with colors</item>
        <item>Added option for s8 launcher with support for s8 Google widget</item>
        <item>s8 Lockscreen and Weather font</item>
        <item>Build.prop tweak for speaker phone</item>
        <item>Secondary toggle text color. E.g. The wifi ssid name</item>
        <item>Panel Handler color, conforms to global switch</item>
        <item>Simple lockscreen weather color feature</item>
        <item>Set low battery warning notification</item>
        <item>Set critical battery warning notification</item>
        <item>Added Power Menu background for MM Style</item>
        <item>Ambient Display with switch option in rom control</item>
        <item>Full Samsung Music color mod</item>
        <item>Battery text color implemented with tint working at the same time</item>
        <item>Now use tint and color at the same on statusbar icons. Tint on white background and color on dark background</item>
        <item>Toggle animations applied when global toggle set to stock</item>
        <item>Toggle help text color which also conform to global switch</item>
        <item>Fixed Off Screen Memo</item>
        <item>Fixed Stock SystemUI flashlight settings</item>
        <item>Turn OFF flashlight from notification panel</item>
        <item>Battery Bar reworked with more options. Now possible to select gradient</item>
        <item>Custom Carrier label rework. More option added</item>
        <item>Aroma option for Chainfire Systemless rooting</item>
        <item>Aroma option for system mode rooting - patching to make it system mode install</item>
        <item>Aroma option for Magisk rooting. Includes Magisk manager and SuperSU</item>
        <item>Global switch to restore all notification colors to stock for theme applications and original stock look</item>
        <item>Bluetooth Share FC on Systemless root should be fixed</item>
        <item>Same color switch for statusbar icon</item>
        <item>C9 Smart Manager aroma option removed as some were confused with this. Can be installed in rom control</item>
        <item>Added option for s8 launcher with support for s8 Google widget</item>
        <item>Custom carrier now keeps color after a restart</item>
        <item>Rom control UI rework for some preferences and few things tidy up</item>
        <item>Fixed clock color disappearing after each restart for Potato clock and Phronesis Style clock</item>
        <item>Kernel Updated. Now at 1.2g. Fixes call issues for people that experienced it. And other improvements</item>
        <item>Kernel add-on path updated</item>
        <item>Better support for systemless rooting</item>
        <item>A lot of applications updated. Over 20 apps for this release</item>
        <item>And a lot more changes which has not been mentioned here. Please visit our rom thread of full changes</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--This will be the dialog title.
    Put your own rom version and name.
    Have fun-->
    <string name="rom_version_for_changelog">Phronesis N7 Port V6</string>


</resources>